tvprocessing.com 2011-11-02

# TVprocessing - The Best TV Affiliate Network

**Privacy Policy**

Effective February 11, 2008

**Changes to this Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may occasionally change. Any Policy changes will be posted to this page. Each version of this policy will be denoted at the top of this page by its effective date.

**Privacy Policy**  
We, at [TVProcessing.com](http://www.tvprocessing.com/) respect your right to privacy and we are committed to protect it.  
This statement discloses the information that we gather and track, how we use the information, and with whom we share this same information.

**Personal Information**  
You can visit any of our web site without indicating to us who you are and without revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to buy from this web site, we ask you to provide basic information such as your First Name, Last Name and e-mail address. This will be used to set up your private account, invoice and send your purchase confirmation. Your personal information will NEVER BE DISCLOSED OR SHARED WITH ANY THIRD PARTY without your explicit consent. If you _do not_ wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our customization programs, simply indicate your preference once you sign-on to this web site.

Transactional information such as credit card details, billing address and/or phone number are required to purchase and activate your membership. If you provide us with personal information or credit information about somebody else, such as a family member, friend or associate, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.

**Fulfilling your Transaction Request**  
To fulfil to your request (i.e. access to our customer’s area, technical support, etc.), you agree that we may use your personal information to identify you as a client.

**Information Security**  
We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. To help us keep your information secure and maintain its quality, we implemented appropriate measures and processes, such as SSL encryption when transmitting sensitive information.

**Cookies and Other Web Technologies**  
A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. To help us provide better customer service, we sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Web sites. 

We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". Some of our pages use cookies, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You also can set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly. For example, we may keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we may also measure visitor activity.

**Security, Intrusion, and Detection**  
For website security purposes, and to ensure that our website remains available to all visitors, all network traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage or conduct criminal activity. To protect the system from unauthorized use and to ensure that the system is functioning properly, individuals accessing our website are subject to having all of their activities monitored. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this service, are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable federal law.

**Contact Information**

[TVProcessing.com](http://www.tvprocessing.com/) welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you have any questions regarding our Statement of Privacy or this website, please contact us.
